SIGN IN USER

Your account Sign out

SIGN IN USER

Your account Sign out

Our Privacy Statement & Cookie Policy

By continuing to browse our site you agree to our use of cookies, revised Privacy Policy and Terms of Use. You can change your cookie settings through your browser.

I agree

Privacy Policy

**Last updated: December 6, 2024** 

**Effective date: December 6, 2024** 

China Global Television Network (collectively referred to as "CGTN" or "we", "us", or "our"), it is important for us to protect your personal data at all times. Therefore, we will comply with the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), California Consumer Privacy Act (CCPA), the Personal Information Protection Law (PIPL) of the People's Republic of China and other applicable personal data protection laws, adopt security protection measures to formulate CGTN Privacy Policy (hereinafter collectively referred to as "this Privacy Policy") to protect your personal data. Please read this Privacy Policy in conjunction with the User Agreement.

This Privacy Policy applies to our websites you visit, the data collection and processing performed, and the use of our products and services. This Privacy Policy covers how we collect and process your personal data when you log on to and use our website services worldwide.

According to the applicable personal data protection laws, the information of data controllers and data protection officers is as follows:

Name of data controller: Company: China Global Television Network Corporation

Address: Room 2210, Building 2, No.1 XiDaWangLu, ChaoYang District, Beijing, People's Republic of China

Data Protection Officer in Europe  
Name: iuro Attorneys at Law represented by Dr. Andreas Maetzler  
E-Mail: cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com

Tip.  
**If you are under 18 years of age, please do not provide any personal data without the permission of a parent or legal guardian. (If you are in Thailand, Singapore, Indonesia, etc., we consider users under the age of 21 to be children.)**

**Before using CGTN products and services and submitting your personal data, please read this Privacy Policy carefully and make sure that you fully understand and agree to it before using it, and that you are fully aware of and understand the meaning of its contents and the corresponding legal consequences. By signing, or clicking "read", "agree" or other similar options, and submitting your personal data to us, you are deemed to have accepted this Privacy Policy.**

Unless otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy or required by laws and regulations, when we need to use personal data for purposes not specified in this Privacy Policy, we will inform you in advance and obtain your consent through pop-up notifications or other means.**Refusing to agree to this Privacy Policy will not prevent you from using our website; however, doing so may prevent us from recommending news and videos to you. If you use CGTN services without registering or logging in, we will provide you with browsing services in guest mode. In guest mode, we can only offer limited features, and to ensure these features work, we will collect your cookie, IP, device information, and other data.**

The CGTN products and services described in this Privacy Policy may vary depending on the model, system version, software application version, etc. of the cell phone you are using. The final products and services are subject to the CGTN products and services you use.

**Among them, we use bold font or other reasonable ways to identify the terms that are (may be) significant to your rights and interests, and you should focus on reading them. If you have any questions, comments or suggestions regarding this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through Part 10 of this Privacy Policy.**

This policy will help you understand the following.

1.Definitions and legal basis  
2.How we collect and process your personal data  
3.How we provide, disclose and store your personal data  
4.How we protect your personal data  
5.Your rights  
6.How we process minors' personal data  
7.How your personal data is transferred globally  
8.Use of cookies and similar technologies  
9.How this policy is updated  
10\. How to Contact Us

I. Definitions and legal basis

**Section 1. Definitions**

Personal data: refers to any data related to an identified or identifiable natural person (data subject); an identifiable natural person is one who can be identified directly or indirectly through identifiers such as name, **identity card number, location data,** network identifier, etc., or through specific personal attributes of the body, mind, genes, state of mind, economy, culture, society and so on.

Special categories of personal data: refers to personal data such as **racial or ethnic origin, political views, religious beliefs, philosophical beliefs, labor union membership,** and other personal data, as well as **personal genetic data, biometric data, health data, sex life, sexual orientation** and other related data.

**In this Privacy Policy, the provisions concerning special types of personal data are marked in bold font to draw your special attention to them. In the case of actual collection of special personal data, we will obtain your separate consent.**

**Section 2. Legal Basis**

We collect and process your personal data in strict compliance with the law and the provisions of this policy. We do not normally collect personal data directly from any other source than the data subject, and we collect and process your personal data for the purposes described in this privacy policy. In cases where the collection of special categories of personal data, cross-border transfers of data, etc. are (potentially) of significant relevance to your rights and interests, we will notify you by means of enhanced notification or instant alerts (e.g., pop-up reminders) and obtain your explicit consent.

**We will generally collect, use, disclose or otherwise process your personal data with your consent or in accordance with the law for the purposes described in this policy, including but not limited to the following circumstances:**

1.The data subject has given consent to the processing of his or her personal data for one or more specific purposes;

2.Processing is necessary for the performance of the contract with you or for the performance of the actions you require prior to entering into the contract;

3.Processing is necessary for compliance with legal requirements and fulfill legal obligations;

4.Processing is necessary in order to protect the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person;

5.Processing is necessary for the performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the controller;

6.Processing is necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by the controller or by a third party.

II. How we collect and process your personal data

We collect and process your personal data in accordance with applicable personal data protection laws such as GDPR, CCPA and PIPL. We collect and use your personal data for the following purposes as described in this Privacy Policy. We do not carry out automated decision-making algorithm activities or personalised recommendations based on the personal data we collect from you.

**Section 1. When you use CGTN products and services and agree to this Privacy Policy, the purpose and type of personal data we collect from you**

1.When you use CGTN products and services, we will collect your personal data under the following specific circumstances:

| The products or services provided to you | Personal data types | Purpose |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Email Subscription | Email | Collect your **email address** to verify the validity of your account by sending an email and may use the email address you provide to notify us of products and services offered. |     |
| User Registration/ Login | Telephone number, Email, nickname, birthday, IP address | Collecting your **telephone number、 Email** for registration, to verify the validity of your account by sending an SMS verification code.  <br>your **nickname** collected for registration, for the system identification mark of this account, so that the system and other users can accurately distinguish the services provided to you.  <br>Please note that in order to improve the user experience, after you have successfully logged in, we will provide you with a checkbox for your **date of birth** in the "Your Account" - "Personal Information Edit" page, which you can choose to fill in or not; if you fill in, we will combine your **IP address** and date of birth to identify whether you are a minor or not. If you fill in the checkbox, we will combine your **IP address** and date of birth to identify whether you are a minor.  <br>In order to improve your experience, we will provide a third-party platform for website login, but we will not obtain any of your personal information through the third-party Apple account/Google account/Facebook account/X account/WeChat account, and any authorizations and consents you have given based on the previous version of the Privacy Policy will not be changed in any way. |
| User Comments | Comment content, like data, favorite data, share data, IP Address, Interest words, Browsing history . | To collect your **user comment content, like data, favorite data, share data, IP Address, interest words, browsing history**, to measure and improve our products and services and to create a personalized experience for you.  <br>If you are a user in mainland China, in accordance with the requirements of relevant laws and regulations, we will display your IP address when you post a comment, so that the public can monitor for the public interest. |
| **Community Services** | **Post data, comment data, community data, image and text data, poll data, attachment data** | **We collect your post data, comment data, community data, image and text data, poll data, and attachment data to provide you with community management services, as well as services for posting, commenting, and managing posts.** |
| Website operation, operation and maintenance | cookies, views, click-through rates | Cookies data is collected in order to estimate the number of visitors on our website and the pages that users visit. **Views, click-through rates** is then used to improve the website and its content. To ensure the stability and accuracy of our statistical analysis services and to continuously optimize our services. |

2.We do not collect special kinds of personal data about you, such as data about your race, political opinions, religion, unless you voluntarily provide it to us.

3.We will only request your authorization to enable permissions when needed for you to use the following products or services

To provide the relevant products and services, besides the personal data you provide yourself, we may also need you to authorize the following permissions. Refusal to enable these permissions may result in our inability to provide the relevant products or services.

See the table below for details:

| **Device Permissions** | **Situation Description** | **Purpose of Access** |
| --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Photo Album Access** | **When you use features such as posting, we may need to enable access to your photo album.** | **For uploading and posting photos.** |     |

4\. In addition, the purposes and types of personal data we may collect from you when you visit the CGTN website or when you are not registered to log in to the CGTN website and agree to our privacy policy.

(1) We collect your data in order to satisfy your use of CGTN to access, share, retrieve, jump, copy, fill out forms, and other products or services. Specific scenarios include, the following.

* Providing you with updated data on the services used.
* Responding to your requests via forms on our website and applications.
* Push notifications, alert data to you.
* Data analysis and statistical studies implemented for the purpose of updating and optimizing the order of our website or understanding our website users, research and analysis of our content and services.
* We collect data for data security reasons and to ensure the stability and reliability of our systems, as well as to protect them from possible external attacks.

(2) With your consent, certain data may be collected through cookies or similar technical means (such as IP address, connection and browser data, location data.) as a result of your behavior on the Site.

5\. When you use the product through mobile devices (non-APP), we may call your acceleration sensor, orientation sensor, gravity sensor permissions, detect the screen direction change, video playback horizontal firm screen switch heart. Through your sensor information (individual sensor information is not personal information) to provide you with the corresponding business functions. Please be aware that individual device sensor information does not involve any person's location information and cannot be combined with other information to identify an individual.

**Section 2. Exceptions to consent**

CGTN will process your personal data with your consent and regard your consent as the legal basis for collecting and processing personal data. The purpose of processing personal data and the types of personal data that need to be processed are explained in detail above. If you have any questions about our personal data processing activities, please feel free to contact us through the contact information published in Part 10 of this policy.

Please be informed that, according to applicable laws and regulations, CGTN has the right to process your personal data without obtaining your prior consent in the following circumstances:

1.Processing that must be carried out to perform a contract to which the personal data subject is a party or to meet the pre-requirements put forward by the personal data subject in entering into the contract;

2.Processing necessary to fulfill the legal obligations assumed by the controller of personal data;

3.Processing necessary to protect the vital interests of personal data subjects or other natural persons;

4.Processing necessary for the public interest or to carry out the official powers conferred on the controller of personal data;

5.Processing that must be carried out based on the legitimate interests of the controller of personal data or third parties. Personal data should be protected if the requirements of the rights, fundamental rights and freedoms of the subject of the personal data are more important than the aforementioned legitimate interests, especially where the subject is a child, that is, the aforementioned exception without prior consent for the processing of personal data does not hold.

III. How we share, publicly disclose, and store your personal data

**Section 1. Share**

We will not share your personal data to any company, organization or individual, except for the following.

1.Shared under the condition of obtaining separate consent. After obtaining your separate consent, we will provide your personal data to other parties.

2.In the event of a merger, acquisition or bankruptcy or liquidation involving the provision of personal data to the successor of the company's rights and obligations, we will separately inform you of the situation and request that the new company or organization holding your personal data continue to be bound by this privacy policy, or we will require the company or organization to seek your authorized consent again.

**Section 2. Publicly disclose**

We will only publicly disclose your personal data if

1.When it is necessary for our business and after obtaining your consent.

2.Publicly disclose based on law: We may disclose your personal data when compelled to do so by law, legal proceedings, litigation or government authorities.

**Section 3. Storage**

1.We will store the collected personal data on our servers according to the requirements of laws and regulations. At the same time, we securely store the personal data we collect in accordance with laws and regulations and the most advanced cyber security practices.

2.Storage Term We store only for the time necessary to achieve the purpose of processing or to fulfil our contractual or legal obligations. Will not exceed the time necessary to process personal data, unless a longer period of time is required for legal, regulatory or procedural purposes. However, when the technical and organizational measures required by law are met, and are only used for public interest, scientific or historical research and statistics, they will be stored for a long time.

3.After the retention period expires, your personal data will be deleted from the system or anonymized.

4.For countries with localized storage requirements, we will actively communicate with your country or region to jointly achieve localized storage.

IV. How we protect your personal data

**Section 1.** We have used security measures and organizational measures that meet industry standards to protect the personal data you provide from unauthorized access, public disclosure, use, modification, damage or loss. We have passed the China Network Security Level Protection (Level 3) classification and have established a good coordination and communication mechanism with regulatory agencies and third-party testing and evaluation institutions to timely resist and deal with various information security threats and provide comprehensive protection for your information security. We use encryption technology to ensure data confidentiality; we use trusted protection mechanisms to prevent malicious attacks on data; we deploy access control mechanisms to ensure that only authorized personnel can access personal data. We establish a dedicated privacy compliance organization and management system for employees, suppliers, etc. We hold regular security and privacy training courses to enhance employees' awareness of the importance of protecting personal data.

**Section 2.** We will take all reasonably practicable steps to ensure that only personal data necessary for the purposes described in this policy are collected. We will only retain your personal data for as long as is necessary to achieve the purposes described in this policy, unless there is a genuine need to extend the retention period and obtain your separately authorized consent or in accordance with laws, regulations or special regulatory requirements regarding data retention periods.

**Section 3.** The Internet environment is not 100% secure, and while we are committed to protecting your personal data, we cannot guarantee or warrant its absolute security. Therefore, you should also take active steps to ensure the security of your personal data.

**Section 4.** After the unfortunate occurrence of a personal data security incident or in the event of a data breach, we will, in accordance with the requirements of laws and regulations, promptly inform you of: the basic situation of the security incident and the possible impact, the disposal measures we have taken or will take, the suggestions you can independently prevent and reduce the risk, the remedial measures for you, etc. We will promptly inform you of the incident by email, letter, telephone, push notification, etc. When it is difficult to inform personal data subjects one by one, we will take reasonable and effective ways to issue announcements. If you have any questions about our personal data protection, for example, if you find that your personal data has been leaked, please contact us immediately via the contact information in Part IX so that we can take appropriate measures. At the same time, we will also take the initiative to report the disposition of personal data security incidents in accordance with the requirements of the regulator.

**Section 5.** Some search engines, social media, friend links and other products or services may contain web links operated and maintained by third parties, but we have no control over such third parties. Please note that any data you provide to a third party will be subject to the terms of that third party's privacy policy or personal data protection policy. We encourage you to understand and ask questions before providing any data to a third party. We are not responsible for the content, conduct or policies of third parties. The presence of a link to a third party on some of our products and services does not mean that we endorse the content, conduct or policies of that third party.

V. Your rights

In accordance with the provisions of the law and the prevailing practices in other countries and regions, we protect your right to exercise the following rights with respect to your own personal data.

**Section 1. Access, review and copy your personal data**

You have the right to access your personal data, except for the exceptions stipulated by laws and regulations.

You can access, review and copy your personal data through the website home page → personal page.

You can send us an email to cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com to inquire about your personal data. We will respond to your request no later than one month after verification.

You have the right to request that we provide a copy of your personal data in a structured, commonly used, or machine-readable format under the following conditions:

1.The personal data was collected and processed based on your consent;  
2.The data was collected and processed to fulfill a contract between you and us;  
3.The data was collected and processed through automated means. Additionally, you have the right to request that we transfer your personal data to a third party. As long as it is technically feasible, we will directly transfer your relevant personal data to the third party you designate.

You may exercise your rights by sending an email. Please note that exercising these rights should not adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others. Furthermore, if the personal data you requested to be provided or transferred has already been deleted, or if we are not permitted to provide or transfer your relevant data under applicable laws and regulations, we will not be able to respond to the above-mentioned rights.

**Section 2. Deletion of your personal data**

You may make a request to us for deletion of personal data in the following cases.

1\. if we process personal data in violation of laws and regulations.

2\. If we collect and use your personal data without your consent.

3\. if we process personal data in violation of the agreement with you.

4\. if the purpose of processing your personal data has been achieved, cannot be achieved or is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose of the processing (e.g., you no longer use our products or services, etc.)

5\. when we terminate our website services and operations.

6\. when you have withdrawn your authorized consent to our processing of your personal data.

If we decide to respond to your request for erasure, we will also simultaneously notify the entities from which we obtained your personal data to request their prompt erasure, unless otherwise required by law or regulation, or unless these entities have your independent authorization.

When you delete data from our services, we may not immediately delete the corresponding data from our systems because of applicable legal and security technical restrictions, but we will store your personal data securely and will not process it any further. In order to fully protect your personal rights, we may retain the necessary data in our backup systems while keeping such data in a state that is not retrievable or accessible by technical means.

If you need to cancel your CGTN account, please go to the CGTN website Home → Personal → Your account → Delete your account. after you cancel your account, we will stop providing you with all CGTN products and services, and protect your information through anonymization and deletion as required by laws and regulations.

If you are unable to cancel your CGTN account by the above means, you may send an email to cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com. We will respond to your request no later than one month after verification.

**Section 3. Correction of your personal information**

When you discover that the personal information, we process about you is incorrect or incomplete, you have the right to ask us to make corrections. You can correct it yourself by the following ways.

You can improve your personal data by going to the homepage of the website → Personal page.

If you are unable to correct such personal data by the above means, you may send an email to cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com. We will respond to your request no later than one month after verification.

**Section 4. You may restrict our processing of your personal data in the following circumstances.**

1\. the data subject questions the accuracy of the personal data and the controller is allowed a certain period of time to verify the accuracy of the personal data

2\. the processing is unlawful and the data subject objects to the deletion of the personal data and requests that the use of the personal data be restricted

3\. the personal data is no longer required by the controller for the purposes of the processing, but the data subject requires the personal data for the establishment, exercise or defend of a legitimate right.

4.You have objected to the processing of data, and are awaiting verification of whether the legitimate interests override those of the data subject.

**Section 5. Right to object and right to withdraw consent**

If we process your personal data as necessary to pursue our legitimate interests; You have the right to object to the processing of your personal data when performing a task in the public interest or based on official authority, or for reasons relating to your particular circumstances. You can exercise your rights by sending an email.

You have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of personal data at any time, including withdrawing consent for certain types of personal data processing or consent based on a specific purpose of personal data processing. However, please note that this withdrawal does not have retroactive effect. After receiving your request, we will promptly delete your relevant data in accordance with Part 3 of Section 4. You can withdraw your consent by sending an email.

**Section 6. Responding to your request above and complaints**

To protect the security of your personal data, you may need to prove your identity and we will process your request after verifying your identity.

We will respond to your request in no more than one month.

In principle, we do not charge a fee for your reasonable requests, but we will charge a cost fee for repeated requests that exceed reasonable limits, depending on the circumstances. We may refuse requests that are unwarrantedly repetitive, require excessive technical means (for example, requiring the development of new systems or fundamental changes to current practices), pose a risk to the legal rights of others, or are highly impractical.

If you are dissatisfied with the way we have processed your personal data and wish to file a complaint, you may do so by contacting:

* Your national Data Protection Authority which contacts information is located on this [webpage](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en)
* The Cyberspace Administration of China through this [webpage](https://edpb.europa.eu/about-edpb/board/members_en) (in Chinese)

**Section 7. California residents have the following specific legal rights.**

We recognize and protect your legal rights under the CCPA and other California laws. You may exercise your rights at any time in accordance with Part 4 of this Policy. In addition, you also have:

1.Right to know about participating in data sharing in exchange for financial incentives  
If we provide financial incentives before collecting your personal data, we will obtain your consent in advance.

2.The right to choose not to sell personal data to third parties  
You have the right to choose not to sell your personal data to any third party. Please be aware that this right does not apply to the situation where we share personal data with service providers. Service providers are parties we entrust to perform functions on our behalf, and they have a contractual obligation to use personal data only within the scope of their functions as agreed in the contract.

3.The right to be free from discrimination  
You can exercise all rights at any time, and we will not discriminate against you for exercising your rights under the CCPA.

4.California Shine the Light Law  
California residents have the right to request information about third parties to whom the company disclosed certain types of personal data for the latters direct marketing purposes in the previous calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like us to stop such personal data disclosures, you can send an email to us.

Exercising Your Rights: If you wish to exercise any of your privacy rights or have any questions about how we use your personal data, please contact us via email at: cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com.

**Section 8. We will not be able to respond to your request in the following circumstances:**

1\. related to the performance of our obligations under laws and regulations

2\. directly related to national security, national defense security

3\. directly related to public safety, public health, and significant public interests

4\. directly related to crime investigation, prosecution, trial and execution of judgments, etc.

5\. where we have sufficient evidence to show that you have subjective malice or abuse of rights

6\. for the protection of your or others' life, property and other significant legitimate rights and interests but it is difficult to obtain your consent

7\. responding to your request will lead to serious damage to the legitimate rights and interests of you or other individuals or organizations.

8\. involving commercial secrets.

**Section 9. Change the scope of your authorized consent**

To provide you with more accurate and convenient services, we will make comprehensive judgments based on your interest words and behavioral data (comments, favorites, browsing records) and recommend content that you may be interested in. At the same time, to ensure your autonomy in receiving information, if you need to turn off the "Personalized Recommendations (For You)" function, you can turn off the "Personalized Recommendations" function by sliding the key on the right side of the "Home Page-Personal Home Page-For You Board". You can turn off the "Personalized Recommendations" feature by sliding the button on the "Website Home Page - Personal Page - For You Section".

VI. How we process personal data of children

Our products, websites and services are primarily intended for adults. Children are not permitted to create their own user accounts without the consent of their guardian or parents, and if we discover that a child's personal information has been collected without prior verifiable parental consent, we will seek to delete the data as soon as possible.

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, we consider any person under the age of 18 to be a child under the GDPR and the laws of other countries, and we consider users under the age of 14 to be a child under the Personal Information Protection Act (China Mainland); and we consider users under the age of 21 to be a child in countries such as Thailand, Singapore, and Indonesia.

VII. How your personal data is transferred globally

We have a global footprint and sometimes we need to store or process your information outside of your country of residence when using your data, including countries with different levels of legal protection for your data and where you have fewer legal rights.

Before transferring your personal data across borders, **we will re-prompt you and obtain your separate consent by means of an enhanced notice or an immediate prompt** (such as a pop-up window).

Although such jurisdictions may have different data protection laws, we will adopt organizational and technical measures to ensure that your personal data is adequately and equally protected. For example, we will conduct security initiatives such as personal data security impact assessments prior to cross-border data transfers and adopt technical and administrative measures to effectively meet our data security protection obligations.

VIII. The use of cookies and similar technologies

**Section 1. When you visit our website, your cookies are collected and processed by us and by Google Analytics on our behalf.**

Google Analytics uses statistical information collected from our website and your use of our website to analyze information such as click-through rates, the geographical distribution of users, etc. Google Big Query uses information about your use of our website to help us analyze news and videos that may be of interest to you in order to improve the quality of our content. For more details on how Google Analytics and Google Big Query use your personal data, you can visit their [privacy policy](https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites?hl=en) and Google Big Query [commitment](https://cloud.google.com/security/gdpr/) to the GDPR. Our Sites and Services use cookies and similar technologies to help us collect other data. The Sites and Services may also include third-party cookies and similar tracking technologies that may collect other data about you through the Sites and Services and other websites and online services.

**Section 2.** A cookie is a small text file that is stored on your computer to identify and remember you. It is sent to your browser and stored on your computer's hard drive, tablet or mobile device. When you visit our website, we may collect data about you through a cookie or similar technology. For a more detailed explanation of what a cookie is and how it works, please visit the EU Cookie Guide at[https://ec.europa.eu/info/cookies\_en](https://ec.europa.eu/info/cookies_en).

**Section 3.** When you visit our website, we will send a cookie to your device and send it to Google and our servers. We will not use cookies for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy.

**Section 4.** You can change your web browser settings to opt out of our cookies and the browser you can use to perform this action. You can delete all existing cookies on your device by clearing your browser's browsing history, which will delete all cookies from all websites you have visited. please note that you may also lose some saved data. Since most web browsers include the ability to manage cookies, you can change your web browser settings to opt out of our cookies at any time. you can do this for depending on your browser type as follows.

**Section 5. These cookies are essential for the proper functioning of the website. They allow you to navigate the site and use its features freely. Without these cookies, the services you have requested cannot be provided. Please refer to the list of strictly necessary cookies. You cannot disable these strictly necessary cookies as they are crucial for the website to function properly.**

| Cookie Name | Field | Purpose |
| --- | --- | --- |
| Universal Analytics (Google) | AMP\_TOKEN  <br>IDE  <br>\_\_auc  <br>\_ga  <br>\_gat\_newsTracker  <br>\_gat\_webTracker  <br>\_gid | Facilitate users' website usage and help the website understand anonymized browsing volume and the number of unique visitors; does not identify specific users. |
| Search query cookie | user\_id  <br>Event Name  <br>event\_label | Records triggered event information to understand users' actions on the website. |
| gpv  <br>\_ga  <br>\_ga\_id | Provides users with the page paths visited on the website to understand their browsing behavior on the site. |
| Page Path  <br>Device Type  <br>User Agent | Facilitates users' website usage and helps the website understand anonymized browsing volume and the number of unique visitors; does not identify specific users. |
| Website statistics | user\_id  <br>browsing data |

IX. How this policy is updated

Our personal data protection policy is subject to change. If such changes are material, we will automatically assume that your consent has been withdrawn until you agree to the terms of our Privacy Statement again. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your express consent. We will post any changes to this policy on this page. We will keep an older version of this policy on file for your review.

We will also provide more prominent notice of material changes.

Material changes within the meaning of this policy include, but are not limited to

1\. significant changes in our functional modules, such as the purposes for which personal data is processed, the types of personal data processed, how personal data is used, etc.

2\. significant changes in our ownership structure, organizational structure, etc., such as changes in ownership caused by business restructuring, bankruptcy and mergers and acquisitions, etc.

3\. changes in the primary recipients of personal data sharing, transfer or public disclosure.

4\. significant changes in your rights to participate in the processing of personal data and the manner in which they are exercised.

5\. When there is a change in the department responsible for handling personal data security, contact information and complaint channels of us.

X. How to contact us

For questions about this privacy statement, our website or any other issues unrelated to your exercise of privacy, you may contact us at

**1\. China Global Television Network**

Address: Room 2210, Building 2, No.1 Xi Da Wang Lu, Chao Yang District, Beijing, the People's Republic of China

E-mail: [cgtn@cgtn.com](mailto:cgtn@cgtn.com)

**2\. China Global Television Network UK Representative**

Name: Data Protection Officer

Address: 11th Floor,Building 7,Chiswick Park,Lonndon W4 5YG, UK

E-mail: [dataprotection@cgtn-europe.com](mailto:dataprotection@cgtn-europe.com)

**3\. Data Protection Officer in Europe**

Name: iuro Attorneys at Law represented by Dr. Andreas Maetzler

Address for Requests: 11th Floor, Building 7, Chiswick Park, London W4 5YG, UK

E-mail: [cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com](mailto:cgtndpo@cgtncorp.com)

**Please read this Personal Information Protection Policy carefully before clicking "Agree" to ensure that you know and fully understand its contents, especially the meaning of the bolded content and the corresponding legal consequences. By clicking "Agree" and confirming your submission, you are deemed to have accepted this Personal Information Protection Policy, and we will legally use and protect your personal information in accordance with relevant laws and regulations and this policy.**

EXPLORE MORE

CHOOSE YOUR LANGUAGE

DOWNLOAD OUR APP

Copyright © 2024 CGTN.

互联网新闻信息许可证10120180008

Disinformation report hotline: 010-85061466

EXPLORE MORE

CHOOSE YOUR LANGUAGE

DOWNLOAD OUR APP

Copyright © 2024 CGTN. [京ICP备20000184号](http://beian.miit.gov.cn/)

互联网新闻信息许可证10120180008

Disinformation report hotline: 010-85061466
